José Martín Govea López

Software Developer

in www.linkedin.com/in/magovz

https://martingovea.netlify.app

+52 8341544686

Ciudad Victoria, Tamaulipas, México



I am an IT Engineer with 5+ years of experience working with technologies like HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, React, Angular, PHP, Python, SQL. I really enjoy what I do and I am looking for a job opportunity where I can contribute with my knowledge and grow personally and professionally.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer, Vive Metria

- Design and development of web pages.
- Development and maintenance of web applications.
- Obtaining requirements.
- Database administration.

Software Developer, HTA

- Creation and development of designs (Front End).
- Development and maintenance of web applications.
- Database administration.

Software Developer, DMAC

- Design and development of web pages.
- Development and maintenance of web applications.
- Database administration.

Software Developer, Budget Planning Department of Tamaulipas (professional practices)

• Design and development of user interfaces for web and desktop applications.

06/2018 - 09/2019 Ciudad Victoria.

04/2020 - 12/2022

Tamaulipas, México

Ciudad Victoria,

Tamaulipas, México

09/2017 - 06/2018

Ciudad Victoria,

Tamaulipas, México

11/2015 - 12/2015

Ciudad Victoria, Tamaulipas, México

SKILLS

Knowledge of HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Gulp.js.

PHP, Python.

Experience with frameworks and development libraries (Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, React, Angular, Laravel, Django).

SQL.

PORTFOLIO

https://martingovea.netlify.app

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native) • English (Intermediate)

EDUCATION